<resources>
    <string name="app_name">insta</string>
    <string name="title_activity_home_screen">Home_screen</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="nav_header_title">Android Studio</string>
    <string name="nav_header_subtitle">android.studio@android.com</string>
    <string name="nav_header_desc">Navigation header</string>
    <string name="info">info</string>

    <string name="menu_home">Home</string>
    <string name="menu_gallery">Gallery</string>
    <string name="menu_slideshow">Slideshow</string>
    <string name="menu_tools">Tools</string>
    <string name="menu_share">Share</string>
    <string name="menu_send">Send</string>
    <string name="title_activity_home">home</string>
    <string name="shop">Shop</string>
    <string name="Insta">Insta</string>
    <string name="plants">Plants</string>

    <string name="google_auth_code">858051259543-h4st1lc1hng95dv5hifv7q8oa60jvt15.apps.googleusercontent.com</string>
    <string name="title_activity_map">map</string>
    <string name="sch1">PM KISAN SCHEME</string>
    <string name="sch2">Pradhan Mantri Krishi Sinchayee Yojana (PMKSY)</string>
    <string name="sch3">Paramparagat Krishi Vikas Yojana(PKVY)</string>
    <string name="sch4">Gramin Bhandaran Yojana</string>
    <string name="sch1_d">The Rs 75,000-crore PM-KISAN scheme was announced in the interim budget, under which the government decided to provide Rs 6,000 per year (in three equal installments) to an estimated 12.5 crore small and marginal farmers holding land up to 2 hectares.The revised scheme envisages to cover two crore more farmers with an estimated expenditure of Rs 87,217.50 crore in the 2019-20 fiscal.
The Centre has also asked state governments to use "the existing land ownership system" to identify beneficiaries and transfer the benefit after the family details are uploaded on the PM-KISAN portal.</string>
    <string name="sch2_d">PMKSY has been conceived amalgamating ongoing schemes viz. Accelerated Irrigation Benefit Programme (AIBP) of the Ministry of Water Resources, River Development and Ganga Rejuvenation (MoWR,RD and GR), Integrated Watershed Management Programme (IWMP) of Department of Land Resources (DoLR) and the On Farm Water Management (OFWM) of Department of Agriculture and Cooperation (DAC). The scheme will be implemented by Ministries of Agriculture, Water Resources and Rural Development. Ministry of Rural Development is to mainly undertake rain water conservation, construction of farm pond, water harvesting structures, small check dams and contour bunding etc. MoWR, RD and GR, is to undertake various measures for creation of assured irrigation source, construction of diversion canals, field channels, water diversion/lift irrigation, including development of water distribution systems. Ministry of Agriculture will promote efficient water conveyance and precision water application devices like drips, sprinklers, pivots, rain-guns in the farm “(Jal Sinchan)”, construction of micro-irrigation structures to supplement source creation activities, extension activities for promotion of scientific moisture conservation and agronomic measures</string>
    <string name="sch3_d">According to a 2013 study conducted by the International Federation of Organic Agricultural Movements (IFOAM), there are about two million farmers across the globe who practice organic farming methods and roughly 80 percent of these farms are in India. It wouldn’t be wrong to assume that our country is at the centre of an organic revolution that is set to take the world by storm. Certified or not, the abundance of organic farms in India is certainly not surprising since it is only a continuation of the age-old farming practices followed by our ancestors</string>
    <string name="sch4_d">Under this Gramin Bhandaran Yojana or Rural Godown Scheme, government provides supports to an individual, a company, a farmer , local government, NGOs Gramin Bhandaran Yojana, announced in 2001, is a capital investment subsidy scheme for renovation and construction of rural godowns. Godowns should, however, be constructed outside municipal corporation limits. It is important to note that rural godowns (promoted by Ministry of Food Processing) which are located in food parks can also avail of Gramin Bhandaran Yojana.</string>
    <string name="sch1_l">http://www.pmkisan.gov.in/</string>
    <string name="sch2_l">https://pmksy.gov.in/</string>
    <string name="sch3_l">https://pgsindia-ncof.gov.in/pkvy/index.aspx</string>
    <string name="sch4_l">https://pib.gov.in/newsite/mbErel.aspx?relid=96201</string>

</resources>
